<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob J. Bukoski, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacob J. Bukoski, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jacobjbukoski.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CoderPortfolioの特徴</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio.ja/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio.ja/</guid>
      <description>変更点 ShortCode &amp;ldquo;private content&amp;rdquo;を追加しました 綺麗なサイトを崩さずに、あなたの個人的なコンテンツ（趣味や感情）を簡単に伝えることができます。
実際の動きについては、&amp;rdquo;テーマデモ&amp;rdquo;をご覧ください。
リンクに赤い下線のアニメーションを追加しました サイトがよりカラフルに美しくなりました。
SNSシェアのボタンを追加しました あなたの記事がより影響力を持つようになりました。
コードのハイライトを変更しました 日本のサービス Qiita のハイライトを参照しました。
とても優しく美しいハイライトです。
ヘッダーに影を追加しました より境界線がはっきりしました。
ShortCode &amp;ldquo;portfolio&amp;rdquo;を追加しました あなたの作品を綺麗に表示できるようになりました。 実際の動きについては、&amp;rdquo;テーマデモ&amp;rdquo;をご覧ください。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features Of CoderPortfolio</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio/</guid>
      <description>Change Point &amp;ldquo;private content&amp;rdquo; short code added. It is now possible to communicate your personal hobby and your own content.
You can use it easily. Please see &amp;ldquo;theme-demo&amp;rdquo; for details and demo.
An animation of red underline was added to Anchor. The site became a little fun and colorful.
The button of the SNS share was added. It became to have an influence when writing articles more.
Changed the color scheme of code highlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>テーマデモ</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/theme-demo.ja/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/theme-demo.ja/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/about/</guid>
      <description>--
  Jacob (he/him) is an Assistant Professor and the Director of the Forests and Climate Change graduate certificate at Oregon State University&amp;rsquo;s Department of Forest Ecosystems &amp;amp; Society. His research focuses on the conservation, management, and restoration of forests, globally. Through his work, he has been fortunate enough to work in forests across the globe - including Thailand, Vietnam, Vanuatu, Brazil, California, and New England. Previously, he was a postdoctoral associate at Conservation International&amp;rsquo;s Moore Center for Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Opportunities I will be recruiting graduate students in the Department of Forest Ecosystems &amp;amp; Society for Fall 2023. Please check back soon for graduate school opportunities at OSU&amp;rsquo;s College of Forestry!
Contact guidelines I encourage enthusiastic undergraduates and prospective graduate students to reach out. However, I receive a large number of emails and although I do my best to respond to all, your email may slip through the cracks. To help me get back to you in an efficient manner, please do the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer-Reviewed Articles [17] Melikov, C., Bukoski, J.J., Ban, H., Chen, J.L., Cook-Patton, S.C., and Potts, M.D. 2023. The effects of management actions on biomass growth in forest plantations. Current Forestry Reports doi:10.1007/s40725-023-00182-5.
[16] Haya, B., Evans, S.G., Brown, L., Bukoski, J.J., Butsic, V., Cabiyo, B., Jacobson, R., Kerr, A., Potts, M.D., and Sanchez, D.L. 2023. Comprehensive review of carbon quantification by improved forest management offset protocols. Frontiers in Forests and Global Change 6(958879).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/research/</guid>
      <description>I am broadly interested in the ecology, management and restoration of forests, with a geographic focus on the tropics and western North America. My research occurs through the combination of different data types and approaches - field inventories, statistical modeling, spatial analyses, and critical document review. Given the interdisciplinary nature of forest management, I apply these to both social and ecological systems. Broadly speaking, I have explored these topics through mangrove forests and monoculture plantations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jacobjbukoski.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobjbukoski.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Philosophy My teaching is based in strengthening students&amp;rsquo; critical thinking skills and has won campus-wide teaching awards. I have taught a number of courses at both undergraduate and graduate levels. I have also co-instructed a number of intensive week-long trainings on the use of open source software for processing of massive spatial datasets and the analysis of forest structure and carbon stock data using Program R.
A select list of the courses and workshops I have taught is provided below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>